Hello Hello friends, welcome once again to Trading Beta ji
YouTube channel.
Friends, ICICI Prudential
Insurance Company Limited has
announced its result for March 2001, which has been a smashing result, friends, the
result has been more than expected, so
friends, let's know, in this video we will
also learn details and fundamental analysis
whether this stock is best for investment or
not, we will discuss everything, but
friends, before that, my request is that to
get more such videos, you should
immediately subscribe to this channel
because you will keep getting news related to Delhi Stock Market here, so
friends, let's move ahead and know
what that news is in details, so let's move ahead,
friends, in the last century, the
share price of ICICI Prudential Life Insurance Company Limited had reached
491, after that it went on the downside
and it had
made 432, finally a good recovery was
seen and it had made more than 454,
finally the market closed at Rs. 450.80 paise  The
market was closed and a
slight decline was seen here,
friends, this is the pimples that come out from Edison,
they have announced their Q4 results in
which they have a
profit of 625 crores, friends, in this quarter,
in the same quarter last year 2020, there was a
profit of 179 crores, so here
friends you can see, you can guess
how much profit the company has made,
after this how much the company is protesting,
friends, ever since this corona virus, people
started getting insurance, many
people got health insurance and many other
insurances, but now people have
started all this, so
a lot of growth has been seen in the insurance sector here,
similarly,
good growth has been seen on this topic here too,
friends, this company is now a
joint venture of both of them with ICICI Bank and it does
insurance work like
product term plan, chill plan, will plan,
helpline, it does all these types of insurance,
friends, if I look at the delivery percentage here, then
from here I am getting a delivery percentage of 45 to 50 percent
and  Here we
also show 1659, 25 kg scattered delivery percentage is also
very good, people are picking up the goods in equal quantities
and keeping them for a long time,
friends, if I talk about returns here then I cannot
say that the returns are very good
but right now there is a boom in this sector, so
you can get to see good returns in future
because here it gave a return of 22%
in one year and in the last two years it has given 23
percent, very high returns are being seen in the rest of the staff,
now but
in this chapter you will get to see a good group here continuously,
friends, friends, the
share holding pattern is also tremendous, 73.4
percent is the share holding of the motor
and here it is very good, that means the
percentage is very good, it has been maintained by the promoter,
FII's share is also very
tremendous, here sixteen percent
share and here DI's is 4.7
percent, friends, if we see here, the
promoters have maintained their holding
continuously, here it is
24.98, it is almost close to that  It has
gradually decreased but it has been maintained
friends and here the foreign
investors have continuously
increased their holdings here, here the
domestic investors are a little bit slow
but they have
reduced their holdings a little and
friends if I talk about net profit then you
can see here right now there is another line of this quarter
here that has not been updated
so see friends last March 2019 there was a
profit of 178 crores here
and this year as I told you
something good, okay so friends
in the last quarter 304 hardship in December
quarter and see double of that in this quarter so
friends you can guess
like the company is growing well and
here if I talk about the sentimental aspect then
here at 727 people are
advising to buy it, only 20% people are
saying to sell it friends that means
80% people here are bold that it should be bought
and that means this is happening to hit both of them
okay  This cross of the company is
also very good, it is average, six, those who might be there,
tell them that cross
tells the financial standing of any company, so here the final
stage average of the company is very good and
look here, the revenue is 3 years CAGR,
their revenue is big with 13.2 percent,
net profit - big with 14.1 percent,
operating profit - big with 15.3, as
I told you, there has been a huge
boom in the health sector as well,
many people are taking health insurance,
many people know about insurance,
due to this, there is a boom in this sector right now,
in the coming time you will
see a good boom, after that friends, this
company is a large cap company worth 64 thousand
896 crores and here its current
price is going up by 452, from the 52-week
high of 538 and the low is ₹300, friends, the
debt of the company is 12 hard and they
also have tremendous cash, 812 crore company is almost debt
free.  This is a very good company friends, so
friends, just like this video so much,
now your brother
gets some motivation, subscribe to the channel
and always keep the bell icon pressed,
your brother will keep making such videos for you, so
friends, bye, I will
meet you with a new video.